<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Seglio</string>

    <string name="app_id">5EDgjGMNvj8Eb5CEjW9uPWB9wARKTSNIJwAN1v2K</string>
    <string name="client_key">6LF6Mnm2t2H8DSiLWtPCwbBVHJw8PBR55BXHrmPq</string>
    <string name="facebook_id">1647137865515798</string>

    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="new_user">New user?</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-2857336060972512/9092854388</string>
    <string name="full_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-2857336060972512/1290385989</string>

    <string name="tc">

*END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT*
\n\n
1. LICENSE

By installing and/or using using Seglio (\"Application \"), you agree that this End User

User License Agreement (EULA) is a legally binding and valid contract and agree to be

bound by it. You agree to abide by the intellectual property laws and all of the terms

and conditions of this Agreement.

Your use of Seglio indicates your acceptance of this license agreement and warranty.

Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Seglio grants to you a limited, non-exclusive,

non-transferable license, without right to sub-license, to use Seglio in accordance with

this Agreement and any other written agreement with Seglio. Seglio does not transfer

the title of Seglio to you; the license granted to you is not a sale. This agreement is a

binding legal agreement between Seglio and the purchasers or users of Seglio.

If you do not agree to be bound by this agreement, remove Seglio from your device.

\n\n

2. DISTRIBUTION

Seglio and the license herein granted shall not be copied, shared, distributed, re-sold,

offered for re-sale, transferred or sub-licensed in whole or in part except that you may

make one copy for archive purposes only. 

\n\n3. USER AGREEMENT
\n
3.1 Personal Use Only

Seglio and all related services (the \"Services\") are available only for your personal, non-

commercial use. You may not use the Services to increase traffic to your application for

commercial reasons or sell a service or product unless you enter into an agreement

with Seglio describing the terms of your commercial use. You may not \"meta search\"

any information relating to the Services, including, without limitation, any posted book

review (the \"Reviews\"). You may not reproduce, distribute, store, broadcast, sell or

sublicense information or content included on the application without obtaining prior

written consent of an authorized representative of App Name. Seglio reserves all rights

not granted herein, including all copyrights.

Please contact Seglio if you are interested in entering into an agreement with Seglio

regarding your potential commercial use of the Services or use the \"Apply to sell books

on Seglio\" link found on the home page for more information.
\n\n
3.2 Use Restrictions

You shall use Seglio in compliance with all applicable laws and not for any unlawful

purpose. \n\n

3.3 Copyright Restriction

This Application  contains copyrighted material, trade secrets and other proprietary

material. You shall not, and shall not attempt to, modify, reverse engineer, disassemble

or decompile Seglio. Nor can you create any derivative works or other works that are

based upon or derived from Seglio in whole or in part.

Seglio\'s name, logo and graphics file that represents Seglio shall not be used in any way

to promote products developed with Seglio. Seglio retains sole and exclusive ownership

of all right, title and interest in and to Seglio and all Intellectual Property rights relating

thereto.

Copyright law and international copyright treaty provisions protect all parts of Seglio,

products and services. No program, code, part, image, audio sample, or text may be

copied or used in any way by the user except as intended within the bounds of the

single user program. All rights not expressly granted hereunder are reserved for Seglio.

\n\n 3.4 Limitation of Responsibility

You will indemnify, hold harmless, and defend Seglio , its employees, agents and

distributors against any and all claims, proceedings, demand and costs resulting from or

in any way connected with your use of Seglio.

In no event (including, without limitation, in the event of negligence) will Seglio , its

employees, agents or distributors be liable for any consequential, incidental, indirect,

special or punitive damages whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages for loss

of profits, loss of use, business interruption, loss of information or data, or pecuniary

loss), in connection with or arising out of or related to this Agreement, Seglio or the use

or inability to use Seglio or the furnishing, performance or use of any other matters

hereunder whether based upon contract, tort or any other theory including negligence.

\n\n3.5 Warranties

Except as expressly stated in writing, Seglio makes no representation or warranties in

respect of this Application  and expressly excludes all other warranties, expressed or

implied, oral or written, including, without limitation, any implied warranties of

merchantable quality or fitness for a particular purpose.
        \n\n

3.6 Governing Law

This Agreement shall be governed by the law of the Indian Government applicable

therein. You hereby irrevocably attorn and submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of

the courts of India therefrom. If any provision shall be considered unlawful, void or

otherwise unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this

License and not affect the validity and enforceability of any other provisions.

\n\n3.7 Termination

Any failure to comply with the terms and conditions of this Agreement will result in

automatic and immediate termination of this license. Upon termination of this license

granted herein for any reason, you agree to immediately cease use of Seglio and

destroy all copies of Seglio supplied under this Agreement. 

\n\n3.8 Modification

Seglio may modify or terminate the Services for any reason, and without notice,

without any liability to you, any other user or any third party. Seglio reserves the right

to modify the Terms from time to time without notice. By accessing this application or

using the Services after any changes to the Terms have been posted thereon, you will

be deemed to have consented to all such changes. Please review the Terms from time

to time so that you will be aware of any changes.

\n\n3.9 Indemnification

You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless Seglio, and each of their

officers, directors, employees, agents, representatives, information providers and

licensors, from any claims, costs, losses, damages, judgments and expenses, including

but not limited to reasonable attorney\'s fees, relating to or arising out of any breach of

this agreement or any use of the Services by you, or by another person using the

Services through you or using your device.

\n\n4. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY

This application and the accompanying files are available for download \"as is\" and

without warranties as to performance or merchantability or any other warranties

whether expressed or implied. This disclaimer concerns all files generated and edited

by Seglio as well.

\n\n5. CONSENT OF USE OF DATA

You agree that Seglio may collect and use information gathered in any manner as part

of the product support services provided to you, if any, related to Seglio.Seglio may also

use this information to provide notices to you which may be of use or interest to you</string>
    <string name="sp">

\n\nChoose a safe locality with considerable crowd presence for the meet.

\n\nAlways complete the transaction in the first meet.

\n\nThe buyer must make sure that the book received matches the details as put up on the app by the seller.

\n\nDo not share your financial information except the one involving the payment.

\n\nSeglio isn’t, in any way, responsible for any actions of the buyer or seller.</string>


    <string name="Test3">Testing final merge test</string>

    <string-array name="departments">
        <item>Select a department</item>
        <item>Aeronautical Engineering</item>
        <item>Agriculture &amp; Irrigation Engineering</item>
        <item>Automobile Engineering</item>
        <item>Bio-Medical Engineering</item>
        <item>Chemical Engineering</item>
        <item>Civil Engineering</item>
        <item>Computer Science Engineering</item>
        <item>Electrical &amp; Electronics Engineering</item>
        <item>Electronics &amp; Communication Engineering</item>
        <item>Electronics &amp; Instrumentation Engineering</item>
        <item>Geo Informatics</item>
        <item>Industrial Engineering</item>
        <item>Manufacturing Engineering</item>
        <item>Marine Engineering</item>
        <item>Material Science &amp; Engineering</item>
        <item>Mechanical Engineering</item>
        <item>Petroleum Refining &amp; Petrochemical Engineering</item>
        <item>Production Engineering</item>
        <item>Bio-Technology</item>
        <item>Ceramic Technology</item>
        <item>Food Technology</item>
        <item>Industrial Bio-Technology</item>
        <item>Information Technology</item>
        <item>Pharmaceutical Technology</item>
        <item>Printing Technology</item>
        <item>Rubber &amp; Plastic Technology</item>
        <item>Textile Technology</item>
        <item>Applied Physics</item>
        <item>Applied Chemistry</item>
        <item>Applied Mathematics</item>
        <item>Architecture</item>
        <item>Computer Applications</item>
        <item>Electronic Media</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="contact">
        <item>Choose contact mode</item>
        <item>Email</item>
        <item>Phone and Email</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="shout_outs">Shout outs to Krishna for the vectors, Karthiknathan for the app icon and Mira for the app descriptions.</string>

    <string name="description">Find your now-idle college textbooks a better place than the back of you dusty closet.
    With Biblio, generosity and self-interest go hand in hand. \n\n A quick tap at POST and you can fill out the details of the books
    you\'re looking to see, one at a time. Tap on the account icon to have a look at all your posts and manage them. Buyers can end the hunt for an elusive textbook with SEARCH. Move over to RECENT to view
    the list of books that have been (recently) added. \n\n Time to bid your old books a cheery farewell and welcome your new ones without crashing your bank.</string>

</resources>